But?
- But there will be a price.
- Name it.
- Who was she?
- My sister.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Corporations like Umbrella.
think they're above the law.
But they're not.
There are hundreds of thousands of us
who think the same all over the world.
Some of us provide information.
Others give their support.
Some take more direct action.
Like you.
If your friends had been more thorough.
they would've seen through my false lD.
Then all the red flags
would've gone off.
Quantico. NSA. ViCAP. all the rest.
There's no way I could've
infiltrated the Hive.
So you sent your sister.
We needed something concrete.
anything to expose Umbrella to the press.
Proof of the research
going on down here.
What kind of research?
The illegal kind.
Genetic.
Viral.
My sister was going to smuggle out a
sample of the virus they were developing.
How was she going to make it out?
She had a contact within the Hive.
someone I never met.
They had access to security codes.
surveillance. everything she needed.
So why didn't she make it?
Maybe she trusted the wrong person.
Maybe they set her up.
Kept the virus for themselves.
Do you have any idea what the T-virus
would be worth on the open market?
- Worth all this?
- Yeah.
To someone.
- Don't shoot!
- Close that door!
- They're behind us!
- Close the door!
Get off!
Son of a bitch!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Right behind us.
What about this door?
They're waiting there too.
And that way?
Dead end. There's no way
out of the Queen's chamber.
So we wait.
Someone doesn't hear from you.
they'll send backup or something.
Right?
What? What's wrong?
- We don't have much time.
- Those blast doors we passed
on the way in from the mansion.
they seal shut in under an hour.
If we're not out by then.
we're not getting out.
What are you talking about?
They can't just bury us alive down here.
Containing the incident is
the only fail-safe plan they had...
against possible contamination.
And you're telling us this now.
when we're trapped
- half a mile underground?
- We have to find a way out of this room.
What are you doing?
- Where are you going?
- I'm turning her back on.
- That's not a good idea.
- She'll know a way out.
That homicidal bitch killed my team.
That homicidal bitch may be
our only way out of here.
Considering the way she's been treated.
she'll be real happy to help us out.
That circuit breaker you were
talking about. Can you bypass it?
- Yeah.
- So do it.
Circuit breaker's disabled.
This time. if I hit the switch.
she won't shut down. She'll fry.
The charge must've damaged her boards.
There you are.
Things. I gather.
have gone out of control.
Give me that switch right now.
I'll fry your ass!
I did warn you. didn't I?
- T ell us what's going on down here.
- Research and development.
What about the T-virus?
The T-virus was a major
medical breakthrough.
Although it clearly also possessed
highly profitable military applications.
How does it explain those things?
Even in death. the human body
remains active.
Hair and fingernails continue to grow.
New cells are produced.
And the brain holds a small electrical
charge that takes months to dissipate.
The T-virus provides a massive jolt.
both to cellular growth
and to those trace electrical impulses.
Put quite simply. it reanimates the body.
It brings the dead back to life?
Not fully. The subjects have
the simplest of motor functions.
Perhaps a little memory.
Virtually no intelligence.
They are driven by the basest
of impulses. the most basic of needs.
- Which is?
- The need to feed.
- How do you kill them?
- Severing the top of the spinal column
or massive trauma to the brain
are the most effective methods.
You mean shoot them in the head.
Why did you kill
everybody down here?
The T-virus escaped
into the air conditioning system.
And an uncontrolled pattern
of infection began.
The virus is protean. changing from
liquid to airborne to blood transmission
depending on its environment.
It's almost impossible to kill.
I couldn't allow it to escape
from the Hive.
So. I took steps.
- Steps?
- You must understand.
Those who become infected.
I can't allow you to leave.
- We're not infected.
- Just one bite.
one scratch from these creatures
is sufficient
and then you become one of them.
A check of my systems indicates
my main drive circuit breaker
has been disabled.
May I ask why?
Insurance. We need a way out of here.
If you refuse to help. we flip the switch.
Understand?
After you.
What the hell is this place?
The utility tunnels. They run underneath
the Hive for water. gas and power lines.
- Been in here before.
- Keep moving!
- Going round in circles.
- The computer says...
- Why listen to her?
- Enough!
We have no choice but to keep moving
because those things are behind us.
That mesh won't hold. Keep moving.
- Hold it!
- There's so many of them!
Fuck!
Up on the pipes. Up on the pipes!
Quickly. everyone. up on the pipes!
Come on. there's a way up!
Keep them back!
Go on up. move it!
Get over here. There's too many of them!
Go. go. go!
Go on!
I can manage!
- Rain.
- What?
We have to do something
about your wounds.
I'm fine.
I said I'm fine.
You like that. don't you?
You like the way it tastes. don't you?
Like the taste of that?
She was right.
We're all going to die down here.
No. we're getting out.
All of us.
You OK?
God!
- Hold on!
- Come on!
Help him.
- I can't.
- What are you waiting for?
I can't focus.
I can't see!
- Go up!
- Get up there!
- Come on!
- Go!
- You can do it! Move!
- You got it!
- Stay there.
- We'll get you.
We need to cut this wire and throw it
to him. Then we'll get him.
Hold on.
That's lucky.
I want you to go.
- We're not leaving you.
- Yes. you are.
You can't kill all of them.
I'm not going anywhere.
I want you to go. now!
Please. just do it.
Just do it now!
Please!
Go!
You'll have to work for your meal!
Come on.
Give me your arm. OK?
Over my shoulder.
Ready? Here we go.
When I get out of here.
I think I'll get laid.
You might want to clean up first.
Wait.
Are you OK?
Blue for the virus.
green for the antivirus.
- A cure.
- What are you talking about?
There's a cure.
The process can be reversed.
There's a cure! You'll be OK.
I was beginning to worry.
This is where they kept the T-virus.
How do you know all this?
Because I was going to steal it.
I was your sister's contact.
- You betrayed her.
- I don't know.
- You caused all this.
- I can't remember.
- The truth?
- I don't remember the truth.
I don't understand this.
It's gone. It's gone. It's not there.
I can't.
I just can't. It's over.
I can help you get the virus.
I have access to security codes.
surweillance plans. the works.
- But?
- But there's a price.
Name it.
You have to guarantee me that
you'll bring this Corporation down.
Thank you!
We can still make it out of here.
Come with me.
We can have everything
we've ever wanted.
The money's out there waiting.
You wouldn't believe how much.
Is that how you thought
all my dreams would come true?
Please. I wouldn't want to shoot you.
Might need the bullets.
Back off!
I won't take any part in this.
OK. but you can't just
wash your hands of this.
We work for the same company.
You knew what they did.
I was trying to stop them.
You really believe that people like him
will ever change anything?
Nothing ever changes.
Where...Where is...
the antivirus?
It's on the train.
where you found me.
You couldn't have been standing
more than three feet from it.
I so nearly made it out.
I didn't realise that bitch of a computer
had defence systems outside the Hive.
In or out?
In? Or out?
I don't know what we had.
But it's over.
Back...
the fuck off!
I'm missing you already.
Your boyfriend's a real asshole.
He shot the locking mechanism out.
I can't believe that son of a bitch
is going to get away with this.
I don't think so.
I've been a bad. bad girl.
Oh. my God.
What the fuck is that?
One of the Hive's early experiments.
Produced by injecting the T-virus
directly into living tissue.
The results were unstable.
Now that it has fed on fresh DNA.
it will mutate...
becoming a stronger. faster hunter.
Great.
If you knew it was loose.
why didn't you warn us?
Because she was saving it.
For us. Isn't that right?
I didn't think any of you
would make it this far.
Not without infection.
Why didn't you tell us
about the antivirus?
This long after infection.
there's no guarantee it would work.
But there's a chance. Right?
I don't deal in chance.
Fuck it.
- No pressure. guys.
- You require the four-digit access code.
I can give you the code.
- But first. you do something for me.
- What do you want?
One of your group is infected.
I require her life for the code.
The antivirus is right there
on the platform!
I'm sorry. but it's a risk I cannot take.
She's right. It's the only way.
You'll have to kill me.
Otherwise. we all die down here.
The glass is reinforced.
but it won't hold forever.
Do it.
- Get up.
- Just do it.
- Please.
- Do it!
You don't have long to decide.
- You have no choice.
- Kill her now!
- Get up!
- You don't have any choice.
- Just do it now!
- I can't!
- Kill her now. Do it.
- Please.
- Kill her. Kill her now!
- Just do it.
Kill her!
The bitch wouldn't open the door.
so I had to fry her.
Move!
- What the fuck was that?
- It's a long story.
Start it up.
I'll get the virus.
I'm missing you already.
OK. we're in business.
Full power! We're leaving!
I don't want to be one of those things.
Walking around without a soul.
You won't.
When the time comes...
you'll take care of it.
No one else is going to die.
Here.
I'm not dead yet.
I think I'll have that back.
I could kiss you. you bitch.
What the hell's going on back there?
- Get us the fuck out of here.
- Any faster. we'll come off the rails.
Open the doors!
Open the doors! Now!
I failed all of them.
I failed.
Listen to me.
There is nothing else you could've done.
The Corporation's guilty here. not you.
And we finally have the proof.
And that way. Umbrella
can't get...away with this.
I mean. we can finally...
What is it?
You're infected. but you'll be OK.
I'm not losing you.
- Help!
- Help him! What are you doing?
He's mutating.
I want him in the Nemesis Program.
What's happening?
I want her quarantined.
Close observation
and a full series of blood tests.
Let's see if she's infected.
Take her to the Raccoon City facility.
Then assemble the team.
We're reopening the Hive.
I want to know what went on down there.
Just do it.
Who's in there?
Let me out!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today